http://www.kilsythbasketball.com.au/privacy-policy/

Kilsyth Basketball Website – Privacy Statement
The Kilsyth Basketball respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information.  Personal information is information or an opinion (including information or an opinion forming part of a database) from which it is possible to determine your identity.  Examples of personal information include your name, postal address, telephone number and email address.  We collect personal information in a number of ways, including directly from you if, for example, you provide information to us through this Website.
Kilsyth Basketball has a privacy policy which sets out how it will deal with your personal information.  For a copy of the privacy policy, please contact Kilsyth Basketball on + 61 3 9728 1033.
Share
Latest News
Casual Shooting Bookings
[MORE]
Share
Thursday, December 10, 2020
Team Sheet Fee Decrease for all Domestic Competitions
Following a successful opening week of domestic basketball, we are pleased to announce that we will be reducing all team sheet fees by $5, effective Sunday December 6, 2020.   Currently our team sheet fees have increased due to a number of factors to keep our competitions in compliance with current COVID-19 restrictions. This increase
[MORE]
Share
Saturday, December 5, 2020
Return to Play Information Hub
Welcome to our Return to Play Information Hub. Here we will provide answers to frequently asked questions and important information regarding changes to our competitions and venue operations.   For our latest COVID-19 updates, click here   We will be following Basketball Victoria and DHHS guidelines to ensure that our facilities and operations remain COVID-safe.
[MORE]
Share
Friday, November 27, 2020
Major Partners
DOMESTIC CLUBS
